joke.co.uk 2009-03-29

# View Content - JOKERS MASQUERADE

You are here: Home > Privacy Policy

At Abscissa.Com Limited ("Jokers' Masquerade") we have adopted the following privacy policy as part of our commitment to protect any personal information ("Personal Information") which you may provide to us through this website or by other means. Please note that this privacy policy does not apply to other websites which may be linked through this website. Personal Information which you choose to provide to other websites will be subject to the privacy policies of those websites.

[1] Jokers' Masquerade will not use or disclose your Personal Information unless you have given your permission, except for the following purposes:

[1.1] to assess, operate and improve this website and the services provided through it;

[1.2] to keep you informed about Jokers' Masquerade and its services and about this website;

[1.3] if we are required to disclose such Personal Information by any applicable law, regulation or legal process;

[1.4] to transfer any such Personal Information to other companies within the same group of companies as Jokers' Masquerade, subject to the same privacy policy.

[2] In addition to the use of your Personal Information as described above, Jokers' Masquerade may also gather anonymous information which may be used by Jokers' Masquerade or shared with third parties. This is information which does not identify you, but which may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving this website or the services provided through it.

[3] This website uses, or may from time to time use, cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes and they can make the world wide web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is normal practice and many websites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Cookies do not personally identify an individual user of a computer but they do identify the computer being used. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies.

[4] If you have any questions or wish to have any Personal Information edited or deleted, please e-mail or write to us.

Server: app1.caribbean-abs.islands Timestamp: 3/29/09 10:27 PM Session ID: A6A932F77CF404AC9B83A1E71871D847.jvm1
